Highly motivated technical editor with **two** years of experience in language editing, proofreading, and copyediting.

Motivated negotiator and relationship manager with more than **seven** years of working experience with IT, ITES, UPS, LED, AVR industry.

Over two years of experience in gross margin management.

Over **five** years of experience in direct selling into various industries.

### **Work History**

### 2021-11 -Current

### Freelance Editor/Writer

Freelance, Remote

- Subjects: Electrical and Electronics Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, Civil and Structural Engineering, Computer Science, and Applied Physics.
- Services: copy editing (maintaining tone, grammar and punctuation corrections, rewording and rephrasing of sentences to adhere to flow), proof reading (formatting, spell checks, etc.), cover letter preparation, reviewing of articles based on their content for suggesting additions and deletions, and adherence to target journal guidelines.
- Writing Services: Dissertations (technical/business), essays for MBA, resume writing, ghostwriting, etc.
- 100% deadline conformance.

### 2018-11 -2021-03

## **Assistant Product Manager**

Ingram Micro India Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

- OEMs/Vendors Managed: Lenovo (SMB, Servers), HPI Care packs, CyberPower UPS, and CommScope (Netconnect).
- Effectively handled both back-to-back and stock & sell business models.
- Developed and managed relationships with various vendors and PAN India business partners to ensure revenue and profitability.
- Navigated sales team to achieve revenue by understanding vendor commitments and market dynamics by effectively piloting through cross functional communication.
- Managed discounts to ensure gross margin.

# Sneha Mulye

Technical English Language Editor

### Contact

### **Address**

Pune, India 411015

### Phone

976-924-3994

### E-mail

mulye.sneha@gmail.com

### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sneha-m-a560b557/

### Skills

Attention to Detail

Analytical and Critical Thinkina

Excellent Written and Verbal Communication

Active Listening

Self-Motivated

Interpersonal Communication

Teamwork and Collaboration

Technical Adaptability

Proficiency in Microsoft
Office

Excellent Perceptual Speed

 Sustained PAN India inventory to optimum levels by studying regional markets, historical sales data and current market trends.

 Liquidated ageing stock with pricing support from vendors and running campaigns with help marketing team.

- Achieved 200% quarter-on-quarter growth in Lenovo Server by effective association with vendor, partners, and sales team.
- Increased market share from 29% to 35% thereafter maintained it at 42% just in one quarter for Lenovo SMB by productive alliance with vendor – partner – sales team and effective stock maintenance.
- Revived online and retail sales segment (Amazon, Flipkart, and LES-LMB) to achieve historical sale through.

### 2016-12 -**Executive - Business Development**

Pentagon System and Services Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

- Vendors / OEMs Managed: Vertiv, APC, Luminous, Consul
- Products: UPS with batteries, Inverters, Smart rack solutions, and SCVS.
- Expanded and maintained customers like end users. consultants, and contractors.
- Quoted technically optimum solutions after studying load details and technical specifications. Handled end-to-end sales process thereafter.
- Shaped up vendor alliance for newer opportunities.
- Successfully expanded customer base. Sold up to 120 kVA 3-phase UPS.

#### 2016-01 -**Key Account Manager**

Accutech Power Solution, Mumbai

- Vendor / OEM Managed Vertiv for UPS with Batteries.
- Nourished Key Accounts by grievance resolutions, maintaining rate contract etc.
- Expanded customer base by researching for prospective customers.
- Shared technical quotes with customers after load analysis. Performed end-to-end sales process.

## 2018-10

2016-10

# 2015-01 - **As**

## **Assistant Manager**

7 Greens Solar System Pvt. Ltd., Mumbai

- Handled LED for corporate sector: majorly replacement of conventional fittings by LED fittings.
- Handled incoming enquiries, surveyed sites to quote apt solutions. Made presentations of calculating ROI and attractive payment schemes. Performed end-to-end sales process.

### 2014-05 -2014-11

### **Sales Engineer**

Retail Light Techniques, Mumbai

- Handled both CDMT (conventional) and LED light fittings for Retail Sector.
- Maintained and developed existing customers by grievance resolution, warranty – replacement and rate contracts management.
- Picked up potential end users to generate enquiries, assisted customers with lighting designing and further performed end-to-end sales process.

### 2013-07 -2014-05

## Sales Engineer

Tej Engineer, Mumbai

- Handled engineering products like Automatic voltage regulators, Induction lights, Pumps, and Valves.
- Recognized latent customers to generate leads, surveyed sites, sent out technical quotes, made presentations of ROI calculations, and fulfilled further sales process.

## **Education**

### 2015-12 -2016-12

## Post Graduation Diploma in Management: Advanced Diploma in Business

### Administration

Welingkar Institute of Management - Mumbai

### 2008-07 -2012-07

# Bachelor of Engineering: BE - Electrical (University of Mumbai)

A. C. Patil College of Engineering - Navi Mumbai